<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tinderr</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="tinderr">Tinderr</string>

    <string-array name="friend_names">
        <item>Hasine</item>
        <item>Walla</item>
        <item>Harpreet</item>
        <item>Amandeep</item>
        <item>Yekta</item>
        <item>Natalie</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="friend_full_names">
        <item>Hasine Efetürk</item>
        <item>Walla Smesseim</item>
        <item>Harpreet Kaur-Singh</item>
        <item>Amandeep Singh</item>
        <item>Yekta Valikhani</item>
        <item>Natalie Ching-Yong</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="friend_details">
        <item>Hasine Efetürk was born on 9 February 1992, she comes from a Turkish family of five
            children. She went to the high school Calandlyceum, graduated the Secondary school at
            2008 and graduated the Secondary modern school at 2011. She is now studying Mathematics
            at the University of Amsterdam. She had one long relationship of six years and she is
            single by now.</item>
        <item>Walla Smesseim was born on September 7, 1993, she comes from an Iraq family of four
            children. She has two older sisters, which are both very smart and she also has one
            younger brother. She went to the high school Calandlyceum and graduated the Secondary
            modern school at 2010. She earned her Bachelor title in 2015 at the UU (Utrecht University)
            where she studied Farmacie. She is now doing the master Farmacie as well at the UU.
            She never had a relationship and is interested in something serious. </item>
        <item>Harpreet Kaur_Singh was born on October 31, 1992, she comes from an Indian family of
            three children. She has two older brothers. One of them is already married. She went to
            the high school Calandlyceum. She graduated the Secondary modern school at 2010. After
            that she earned her Bachelor title in 2015 at the VU(free University)where she studied
            Health and Life. She is now doing the master Health Sciences in Rotterdam.
            She has looked around but never found the right one.</item>
        <item>Amandeep Singh was born on May 4, 1993, she comes from an Indian family of three children.
            She is the oldest one. She went to the high school Calandlyceum and graduated the Secondary
            modern school at 2010. She is now in her last year of her bachelor Econometrics. When
            she finishes her study, she wants to find love and marry soon.</item>
        <item>Yekta Valikhani was born on April 4, 1993, she comes from an Iranian family and is the
            only child in the family. She studied Farmacie as well with Walla but after a year, she
            wanted to do something else and choose to study Medicines at the University of Amsterdam.
            She is now in the third year of her bachelor and wants to become a doctor. She has had
            several crushes but it all finished before it was started. She is searching for someone
            to have a good time with.</item>
        <item>Natalie Ching-Yong was born on January 29, 1993, she comes from a Surinamese Czech
            family. She just has one younger sister. She also went to the high school Calandlyceym and
            graduated the Secondary modern school at 2010. She is now in her first year of her bachelor
            Nutrition and Health. She studies at WU, Wageningen University. She has several flows and
            also a few crushes but she never had a serious relationship.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>